I voted for Xu Mengyu,
徐梦予能当主席
and now she's the chair!
还有我的一票
Who's Xu Mengyu?
徐梦予是谁啊
Is she among the candidates?
候选人里面有她吗
You haven't heard of her?
徐梦予是谁你都不知道
She's a renowned talented girl
她可是我们学校
in our school.
赫赫有名的才女
Her mom is the head of
她的妈妈
the Federation of Literary and Art Circles.
是市文联主席
She even published
她在十三岁的时候
her first book
就出版了
when she's just 13!
第一篇文学作品了
I can see why she landed
这人也太厉害了吧
the Student Union presidency
面都没露
without even showing up for campaign.
就当上了学生会主席
Moreover,
最关键的是
she's both talented and beautiful.
她还才貌双全呢
I heard half of the votes
听说呀
she got were from her fans
这里有一半的票
who were smitten by her appearance!
都是她的颜粉
Hey, hear me out!
听我说 听我说
The crazy part is,
最精彩的在后面
Bi Peng was all over the place
只见这个时候毕鹏是
in that tight hallway,
惊慌失措
jumping around,
在这狭窄的走廊里
begging for forgiveness,
是上蹿下跳
then just
连声求饶
bawling his eyes out...
最后是嚎啕大哭
Hey, what are you looking at?
为什么不听我说话
Hi there,
同学
if it's
如果你是来给我
a dating letter,
交友信的话
I'm super busy today.
今天我实在太忙了
Just chuck it here,
你先放我这儿
I'll check it out later.
有空的时候我会看的
Excuse me.
对不起 同学
You're sitting in my seat.
你坐在我的座位上
Mengyu! Finally!
梦予 你终于回来了
You're back.
梦予 你回来了
Mengyu,
梦予 你都不知道
you missed out on a lot
你没来学校的这段时间
during your absence.
学校发生可多事了
I heard you're
你好厉害啊
putting out a book of essays!
听说你要出版散文集了
Where have you been recently?
你最近去哪儿了
I'll answer your questions one by one.
我一个一个回答你们
Ma Yiming, look!
马一鸣 你看这群人
They rushed forward
来 来 来个女孩
when seeing the beautiful girl.
就乌拉乌拉都扑上去了
Only you're the calmest.
还得是你
Jinghui...
灰哥
Mengyu!
梦姐 你没来的时候
I miss you terribly!
我想死你了 梦姐
What's wrong with him?
什么症状啊
Hey buddy, it turns out
同桌 看不出来啊
you're
你是分得
the...
分得清
Where are you going?
你要去哪儿啊
Xiaohua.
徒弟
Qingtian.
晴天
This story
这个故事
is gonna be crazy good later.
后面是真的精彩
Gotta hit the loo first.
我要上厕所
We'll be right back.
回来再说 回来再说
Chen Luyang.
陈璐阳
Call me Mr President.
请叫我主席
Chill out!
别哇了
My story is way more exciting.
我那个比这精彩
Hear me out.
听我说话
Is this how people are?
这就是人心吗
Where's your letter?
信呢 你信呢
You take the lead.
你信呢 先拿出来
Hand over yours first.
你先拿出来
Hurry up.
你快点 你快点
One by one.
一个个给
Xu Mengyu.
徐梦予
Here's the letter I wrote for you.
这是我写给你的信
Thank you.
谢谢
This is my letter.
这是我的
The blue one
还有我的 还有我的
is mine.
这封蓝色的
Let me read it to you.
我先念给你听
Don't.
你别
The smell of sweaty feet
我闻到了好几双
is overwhelming here!
汗脚的脚臭味
Stink!
臭死了
What's your essay all about?
关于什么内容啊
I just shared
其实也没什么
some of my thoughts
就是一些
on life.
我对生活的感悟
Can you change the subject?
能不能问点别的
Hey, quiet down,
你们声音能不能小点
I'm trying to study here.
我还要学习呢
Well... I wonder
那个 徐梦予同学
if you're interested
这周新上映一部电影
in the new movie released this week?
我们要不要去看
Chen Luyang, where are you off to?
陈璐阳 你干嘛去啊
Reading in the hallway.
我 我去走廊读书去
Why there?
去走廊读书干吗
Xu Mengyu's here,
徐梦予都来了
don't you have to
副主席不向主席
report to her
汇报汇报
about recent work?
最近的工作情况
Just filling in as VP for now.
副主席只是暂时的
I'm gearing up for
我在准备
the chair election next year.
明年的主席选举了
My first plan is...
第一个方案是
No election next year.
明年不选举
I've got some other plans.
我有其他方案
Qingtian!
晴天
Your skin's shining,
皮肤也更好了
and you're looking slimmer.
还变瘦了呢
Yeah.
是啊
Mengyu,
徐同学
what are you reading there?
你在看什么书啊
A chemistry book.
看化学
Chemistry is not my strong suit either.
我化学也不太好哎
It's seriously a tough nut to crack.
这道竞赛题的难度最高
Just do your best.
其他同学可以试试
Well...
那个
Sir, I'm Ling Dong.
老师 我叫凌冬
Ling Dong, Chen Luyang.
凌冬 陈璐阳
Since you two
你们俩是我们
are top in the physics subject,
物理竞赛班的前两名
you must figure this one out.
你们俩必须给我做出来
Alright. Let's get started.
好 大家做题吧
Right direction,
你这个方向是对的
but too convoluted.
但不够巧妙
Try to simplify.
绕的弯子太多
Sir.
老师
I'm done.
我做完了
Really?
做完了
I didn't even think of that solution.
这个解题思路
Impressive!
我都没想到啊
Ling Dong.
凌冬
You nailed it fast!
你这么快就做出来了
I'm truly proud of you.
真不愧是我的学生
Ling Dong.
凌冬
You're a genius.
你简直是最强大脑
Don't get
别起哄
too carried away.
别起哄 别起哄
Back to your work.
做你们的题
Genius are rare. What's important
天赋选手本来就不多见
is putting in the effort.
你们需要的是勤能补拙
Well then, sir, I'm leaving.
那老师 那我就先下课了
Bye, sir.
老师再见
Bye.
好
Where are you off to?
去哪儿啊
Wanna eat alone, huh?
吃独食是吧
No. No way.
不行 我告诉你没机会
Hi, Ms Fang.
方老师好
Ms Fang. Thank you.
方老师 谢谢你
It's really thoughtful of you
为了让我们继续养植物
to get us the new rack
还特意给我们准备了
to do plant-caring.
新花架
You like it?
那你们喜欢吗
Yes.
喜欢
Right. We do.
喜欢 喜欢
Good then.
喜欢就好
Well, ma'am,
不过话说回来 老师
what brings you
您来找我们
to us?
是有什么事吗
What?
怎么了
You don't want me here?
我来你不乐意啊
Am I ruining your appetite?
吃不下饭
Gosh, of course not.
没有 怎么可能不乐意
You're so pretty, nice,
老师 您这么美丽 善良
sweet, and generous,
温柔 大方
it's impossible for us
我们怎么可能
to lose our appetite around you.
吃不下饭呢
I could wolf down 3 bowls of rice.
我能吃三碗
Good.
行
Then, I have
那既然是这样的话呢
another good news
我就再告诉你
to share with you.
一个好消息
Cool.
好
After talking to Mr. Zhang,
我和张主任呢
we're gonna set you up
商量以后决定
with Ling Dong
让你和凌冬
in a study group thing.
组成一个学习小组
He'll help you out, one-on-one.
进行一帮一的互助模式
Ling Dong?
我和他
Yes.
对呀
Ms Fang. You must be joking.
方老师 你开玩笑吧
Do I look like
你们俩看我
I'm joking?
像在开玩笑吗
But, ma'am,
不是 老师
what kinda good news is this?
那这算哪门子好消息
What's not good about it?
这怎么不是好消息啊
Ling Dong ranks first
凌冬可是咱们学校
in our grade.
全年级第一
With his help,
有他帮助你
you're sure
你的学习
to make rapid progress.
肯定会进步得很快
Others
而且
are dying to have this.
别的学生想都想不到
So don't be ungrateful,
你别得了便宜还卖乖
study your hardest
你给我好好学 认真学
and don't
别辜负我和主任
let us down.
对你的一片苦心
Ling Dong.
凌冬
You okay with that?
辛苦你了
Alright, I won't
行 那我就不在这儿
disturb you here anymore.
影响你的胃口了
C'mon...
没有
I'm out. Enjoy your meal.
你们继续吃 我先走了
Bye. Ms Fang.
方老师再见
Wait...
不是 方
Why didn't you say no?
不是 你为什么不拒绝
Why didn't you?
你为什么不拒绝
I'm at the bottom of the grade,
我一个倒数第一
I can't change anything.
我拒绝有什么用吗
But if you refused,
如果你提出来的话
she might
他们就会说
have stopped the group
老师影响到我的学习了
'cause I'd
那是不行的
badly impact your studies.
他们肯定就会同意的
No need for that.
没这个必要
And Xiaohua,
还有徒弟啊
no offense,
不是我说你
but can you be sincere
既然要感谢
when expressing your gratitude?
就应该有点诚意对不对
At least ask about my preferences.
你也不问问我的口味
How could I know that you don't like
番茄这么好吃
such delicious tomatoes?
谁知道你不吃
What? They look disgusting!
好吃 看着就讨厌
Why are you staring at me?
你老盯着我干吗
Why don't you eat tomatoes?
你为什么不吃番茄
Why?
我为什么不吃番茄
I don't like that.
我从小就不吃番茄
I haven't liked them
我打小就不爱吃
since I was young.
不爱吃就不吃
Who are you
你谁呀
to ask so much about me?
什么都管
You tell me, my...
你说我是你谁啊 大外
He is...
他
a disaster to me.
他是我的大灾星
You know, disaster.
大灾星
How can you say that?
你怎么可以这样说凌冬
If it weren't for his recording,
要不是因为凌冬的录音
our class wouldn't
那咱们班
have been cleared of injustice.
也不能洗清冤屈
Alright, alright.
好好好 知道了 知道了
You're keep ganging up on me,
前后夹攻
just let me eat my food in peace, okay?
能不能让我好好吃顿饭啦
Sure. Enjoy yourself.
那行 你慢慢吃
Catch you at the study room soon.
一会儿去自习室找我
Who said I'd study?
谁答应你去自习了
I'm off too.
我也先走了
Wait.
等等
Xiaohua.
徒弟
Do me a solid.
能不能帮师傅一件事
What?
什么事
Go to the study room for me, will you?
帮我去自习呗
Xiaohua.
小画
Does he want you to cover for him?
他是不是想让你替他去
Wanna boost your grades?
那你想不想提高成绩
Yeah, for sure.
想啊
I have a plan.
你听我的
But I need your help.
麻烦你帮个忙
I didn't expect Xiao Xiaohua
没想到我刚请假几天
to get so close with Ling Dong
肖小画居然能跟凌冬
while I was out for a bit.
走这么近
All thanks to that Ash Lan.
还不是因为那个渣渣灰
What?
什么
You got Xiaohua to study for you?
你让肖小画替你去自习
Don't you think Ling Dong
你不怕凌冬
will rat you out to Mr. Zhang?
跟张主任告状
So what?
你灰哥我怕过什么
I'm telling you.
我告诉你
I've got beef
我早就看那个凌冬
with him.
不顺眼了
Sitting with him
与其让我跟他
in the study room
待在一块自习
is worse than cleaning toilets.
还不如让我去刷马桶
Lan Jinghui.
兰靖灰
Hey, why are you here?
不是 你怎么来了
But
徒弟
you should be in the study room.
我不让你去自习吗
Asked by Ling Dong.
凌冬让我来的
Lan Jinghui's Don't-Do List?
兰靖灰违禁手册
Go away.
去
I don't want it.
我不要
Wait.
等一下
He asked me to give this to you.
他让我把这个给你
No matter what's written on it,
不管这上面写了什么
I won't even give in.
我都绝对不会去的
Do you want your identity as my nephew
你是想全班都知道
to be made public?
你是我大外甥吗
He said the content above
他说你看到上面的字
is effective for you.
就会明白
What?
写的啥呀
Let me take a look.
你给我看一眼
Get away.
去去去
Stay back.
不许跟过来
Ling Dong took him down
凌冬就用一张纸条
with a single slip of paper?
搞定了
What's on the note?
上面写的啥
I don't know.
不知道
Didn't you read it?
你没看啊
Nope.
没看啊
Why?
你为啥不看呢
Have a sit.
坐吧
C'mon, the same old way, huh?
有意思吗 老用这招
It works, doesn't it?
这招好用啊
Do you now know how much
现在你明白
I care about you as your uncle?
二表舅的良苦用心了吧
I told you
我说过了
no more
不许跟我提这
of that.
三个字
Alright. Hit the books.
那就赶紧的 好好自习
Nephew.
大外甥
Stop there!
也不许提这三个字
Start with this one first.
先把这个做了
You're so scheming, like you've
我说你肚子里是不装的
got a whole library
全是墨水啊
in your gut.
这么腹黑
Homework.
作业
Finish grading these by class end.
下课之前批完给我
Goodbye, Miss Li.
老师再见
Jinghui, let's ball out!
走 灰哥 打球去
Wait.
等会儿
Hurry up.
快点
Tonight's the big clan battle.
今天晚上还有战队赛呢
I got this. Just watch me shine.
我知道 野王重出江湖
I'm bringing my
我让你领略一下
A-game tonight.
哥的风采
Lan Jinghui.
兰靖灰
Done with your homework?
作业做了吗
It's Friday.
今天周五
Oh, right! It's Friday.
提醒我了 今天周五
Yeah.
是的
So you're getting double.
所以作业加倍
Come here.
师父 过来
Lan Jinghui.
兰靖灰
Finish all test papers!
试卷全都要做完
All of them!
全都做完
I can't bear it anymore.
这日子没法过了
What's up?
你干嘛
Nerd.
臭呆子
Excuse me, what's this?
同学 这是什么
You serious?
这你都不知道啊
Basically,
这么说吧
it's a talent show.
就是才艺大赛
Each school sends one representative
每一个学校都选出一个人
to participate in.
来参赛
We've never been absent,
不过我们学校年年参加
but never won either.
年年陪跑
Every other school
其他学校都拿过奖了
has ever taken home the trophy.
就我们学校没拿过
I'm sure you've heard that
想必同学们都知道
the talent show
今年的才艺大赛
sign-ups are live.
已经开始报名了
But it will be
而且今年呢
different
情况比较特殊
this year.
跟往年的情况
You gotta
都不太一样
film yourself
需要同学们录一段
doing your best talent
自己最为得意的才艺
and upload it
上传到我们
to the school website.
校园网站上
Then,
这次的才艺呢
all the students will vote,
会由全校同学统一投票
and whoever gets the most
投票获得第一名的同学
will be the rep.
可以代表学校参加比赛
Now, don't stress
我希望同学们呢
too much about it.
思想包袱也不要太重
Each and every one of you
而且每个同学
have to submit
都必须要录一段视频
a video,
报名参加
okay?
好吗
Okay.
好
Go for it, guys.
希望大家加油
Show us what you're made of.
展现自己最自信的一面
Okay,
好 那我们现在
class time.
开始正式上课
What's your thing?
你有什么才艺
Everyone gotta put up a video.
这必须得传的
I got nothing special.
我没有
Come on. I can show you
没有怎么可能呢
some cool basketball moves.
那我教你花式篮球
You know,
转着花的
spinning the ball on your finger?
转 转 转着花的
You've got too much free time
是不是最近作业太少
on your hands, huh?
闲得慌了
Qingtian. What should we do?
晴天 怎么办啊
We have no choice
方老师让咱们每个人
but to make a video.
都录才艺展示的片段
What's your plan?
你打算录什么呀
I'm set,
我都想好了
just gonna recite some poems.
我就诗朗诵
No way I'm gonna get picked anyway.
反正也选不上
But
可是
I'm not good at anything.
可是我什么都不会
Relax. Xiaohua.
不用担心 小画
No one's gonna
咱们这样的选手
pay attention to us.
没有人会在意的
Just throw something together
你就放心大胆
and call it a day.
随便录一段就好了
Right.
也是
Mengyu, your dance
梦予 你那段舞蹈
is amazing!
跳得也太好了吧
You're leading the vote count
你现在在排行榜上
right now.
可是稳居第一
It's still up in the air with the votes,
现在票数也不稳定
can't say for sure I'll make it.
最后也不一定是我呢
You've got this.
放心吧 梦予
No one can top you.
没有人会超过你的
You're gonna be
你一定会是
our school's rep for sure.
我们学校的代表
Yes.
就是 就是
Mengyu's gonna be
梦予一定是
our school's rep for sure.
我们学校的代表
Hey, cut it out.
你们别这样
You're making me jittery now.
我现在都开始紧张了
Take it easy.
你不要紧张 别紧张
Wait.
干什么呢
It's not even a done deal yet,
现在八字还没一撇呢
and you're already dreaming big.
就代表学校了
I didn't ask for this,
我也不想去啊
but the votes keep coming in my way.
可是大家都把票投给我
What can I do?
我也没有办法
Yeah.
对啊
Mengyu didn't force anyone.
跟梦予有什么关系
Xiaohua.
小画
You still haven't filmed your thing?
你怎么还没录啊
I'm still stuck on what to do.
我还没想好录什么
So, what now?
那怎么办
I'm all thumbs.
我啥也不会
I tried to film last night...
我昨天晚上录
No fear,
徒弟 别害怕
I got your back.
我帮你录
Let's go.
走吧
Qingtian.
晴天
It's okay. I know what to do.
没事 我知道你
Let's go, Ma Yiming.
走了 马一鸣
Hurry!
快点 马一鸣
Uh...
那我 我
what should I do then?
我要做点什么呀
Anything, just get moving.
你就随便做点什么
Move, move, move!
动起来 动起来 动起来
You're moving like a robot.
你这也太像机器人了
I told you that
我就说了
I can't do anything.
我什么都不会嘛
How about dance?
跳舞吧
Dance then. Come on.
跳舞 跳个舞 来来来
Move, move, move.
动起来 动起来
Singing?
唱歌
Singing's easy, right?
唱歌可以吧
Everybody knows how to do that.
唱歌没有人不会唱歌
Okay.
来
Here's a countdown.
我说三二一你就开始
3, 2,1, go!
三 二 一
Let's just scrap this.
要不还是算了吧
Sing whatever comes to mind.
你就随便唱吧
Just do it.
又没有外人 对吧
No one's around to judge.
谁听得见
Okay. Now.
来 可以了
3, 2, 1, go!
三 二 一
♪Out the side of road shelter,♪
长亭外 古道边
♪grasses are green and wild.♪
芳草碧连天
♪Flute wails at night,♪
晚风拂柳笛声残
♪the setting sun in the western sky.♪
夕阳山外山
♪Most friends drift around the world,♪
天之涯 地之角
♪far and wide.♪
知交半零落
♪A cup of wine...♪
一壶浊酒
I don't remember the rest.
我忘了
Okay. Stop.
好 停
It's okay. We've got this.
没事 够了 有了
Perfect.
完美
It's done, Jinghui?
完事了 灰哥
Yes.
完事了
I gotta take care of
但是我还有
something more crucial.
更重要的事情要去做
What's up?
干啥呀
Jinghui.
灰哥
Sorry for that.
不好意思 对不起
Leave me alone.
去 去
Give it back to me.
不是 还给我
You should be studying,
现在是学习时间
so I'm taking this away.
没收了
What?
不是
I'll...
我
do an extra test paper tonight.
我晚上多做一张卷子
Can I get it back?
你还给我
Three.
三张
That's too...
三张是不是有点太
Four.
四张
Alright.
行 行
Four then.
四张 就四张
Hand them over tomorrow morning.
明天早上记得给我
Ling Dong!
不是 凌冬 凌冬
We'll see.
我看你到时候怎么管我
Dear teachers
尊敬的各位老师
and classmates,
亲爱的同学们
good morning!
大家早上好
I'm Ling Dong from Class 5, Grade 11.
我是高二五班的凌冬
I'm excited to share with you
今天我给大家
an article called "Chasing Dreams".
带来的文章是追梦
The existence of dreams
梦的存在
is what gradually shapes our growth.
令我们慢慢成长
Dreams are not just whimsical fantasies.
梦是每一个的梦想
They are the aspirations.
而不是像梦境那般虚幻
Each dream serves as a beacon,
每一个梦想引领着我们
guiding us out of the comfort zone
走出了自己的心境
and into maturity.
脱下了稚气的外衣
During this process,
那么是需要克服
we need to overcome obstacles.
很多困难的
Chasing doesn't
追这个字
simply imply reaching the destination.
不代表达成目标
Look, the composition,
这构图啊
lighting,
这打光
and camera movement...
这运镜
Done your homework yet?
作业写了吗
Don't choose B for all the questions.
这回别都给我选B啊
Why can't I?
为什么不能都选B
I'm a boy,
我是男孩
and I like basketball. I choose B.
我喜欢篮球我选择B
Where are you going?
去哪儿 你要去哪儿
Wait for me.
别别别
Slow down.
慢点 慢点 慢点
I'm losing you!
跟不上 跟不上 跟不上
Yeah.
差不多
It wasn't easy
为了能让你
for me to
顺利参赛
help you get picked.
我容易吗我
Qingtian. What's up?
晴天 你干什么
You gave me a jolt there!
吓我一跳
Ling Dong.
凌冬
What about him?
凌冬怎么了
Check out this video
这是他前不久
he put up recently,
发布的参赛视频
it's blown up and is now in the top ten!
现在已经窜到前十名了
Is that Ling Dong?
这是凌冬吗
Who else could it be?
不是他还能是谁啊
Seriously?
没想到呀
I thought he was
原本以为
all books and no play,
他只是一个冷面学神
but look at him
没想到
go with that dance!
他街舞跳这么好
But something just
但我总觉得
doesn't seem right.
哪里不太对劲
It doesn't quite feel like him.
感觉不像是他
Who else could it possibly be?
这不是他还能是谁啊
What are you doing?
你干吗
Voting for him.
给他投票呀
Don't you wanna see him in the show?
难道你不想看他比赛
Ling Dong, nice moves!
凌冬 你跳得真好
I'll be there rooting for you.
我会给你加油的
Ling Dong,
凌冬 没想到呀
great street dance!
你街舞跳得这么溜
Already voted for you.
我给你投票了
Street dance?
街舞
I think Ling Dong's talent
我觉得凌冬那个才艺
is really impressive.
特别好
I prefer Ling Dong.
我还是喜欢凌冬
Ling Dong, congrats.
凌冬 恭喜你啊
You're number one now.
现在是第一名了
I don't mind
被你超过
being surpassed by you.
我也觉得没什么
I really hope you can become
我是很希望你可以
the rep of the school.
代表我们学校去参加的
If you need any help,
你如果需要帮忙
feel free to reach out to me.
可以随时找我
I've got last year's show
毕竟我去年参加过
under my belt.
还是有经验的
Not my cup of tea.
我对这种事情不感兴趣
Anything else?
还有事吗
Nope.
没事
Ling Dong, congrats.
凌冬 恭喜你啊
Nice editing skills.
合成技术不错呀
Thanks.
没有
You may not be good at dancing,
虽然你底子差
but I'll do everything
但是奈何不住
for you.
我技术高啊
Lan Jinghui.
兰靖灰
I know
你不要以为我不知道
what you're up to.
你想干什么
What?
我想做什么
What am I up to?
我 我想做什么
Please speak out
凌冬同学 请你告诉我
all your thoughts.
我到底想做什么
I...
我想
Let's not waste
我劝你还是
each other's time, okay?
不要浪费时间了
What am I up to?
我 我到底想干什么
Ling Dong. Ling Dong.
凌冬同学 凌冬同学
Congrats. Congrats. Congrats.
恭喜 恭喜 恭喜
Check out that video of the girl
你们看高二五班
from Class 5, Grade 11.
那个女生的视频了吗
It's cracking me up,
太搞笑了
so funny!
超级搞笑
Yeah? I'm out of the loop.
真的吗 我还没看到过呢
Go check it, I even cast a vote for her.
快去看 我都给她投了一票
She can't even sing on key,
她都能进前十
how's she up there in the top ten?
她不是唱得不好吗
Some people voted
大家都是觉得她搞笑
'cause she's funny.
才投给她的吧
Trying to do something
一本正经地
she's not good at with all seriousness,
做自己不擅长的事情
that's hilarious.
就是搞笑啊
Not me. I voted for her.
没有啊 我就投给她了
Because I can see
我觉得她没有很好笑啊
her true side.
反而觉得很真实
Although
虽然不擅长
she's not good at singing,
但专注地做一件事情
her focus on this
让我觉得
has inspired me a lot.
真的挺感动的呢
Alright, I'm gonna vote for her too.
那我也投给她吧
Xiaohua.
小画
Xiaohua. You've reached
小画 你的视频
second place now!
已经冲到第二名了
For real? Don't mess with me like that.
真的假的 你别吓我
I went nuts when I
我刚看到的时候
caught wind of it.
也激动坏了
You sure you're not mistaken?
你是不是搞错了
How'd she pass me?
她怎么可能超过我
Why can't she?
怎么就不可能超过你了
We're all
大家都是两个眼睛
human.
一张嘴
What makes you think
难道你比别人
you're so special?
多一张嘴吗
You...
你
For what?
你什么你啊
Enough, Qingtian.
好了 晴天
This situation
我第二这件事情
is indeed weird.
确实是太诡异了
Anyway,
你放心吧
I won't pose a threat to the first place.
反正我不会拿第一的
Glad you know your limits.
算你还有点自知之明
What's that supposed to mean?
什么叫自知之明啊
Xia Qingtian!
夏晴天
Watch your tone.
你怎么跟梦姐说话呢
So what?
我就这样说话怎么了
You...
你
So rude.
不礼貌
She dissed Xiaohua first.
是她先侮辱小画的
Even so,
那她说小画
you shouldn't be rude.
你也不能没礼貌
Ma Yiming.
马一鸣同学
Watch your tone.
你怎么和同学说话呢
So what?
我这么跟她说话怎么了
Don't talk to
那你也不能跟我们班
girls like that.
女同学这样说话呀
What did I say wrong?
我跟她说话怎么了
I just can't let her...
她就不能欺负
Enough. Stop.
好了 别吵了
Well...
就 就
First place is not gonna be mine.
反正我也不会拿第一的
People are just
大家投我
voting for me for fun.
就是投个热闹嘛
Excuse me.
你好 你好
Please vote for Xu Mengyu.
请给徐梦予投一票
Hi. Please support Xu Mengyu.
你好 给徐梦予投一票
Thank you.
谢谢
Please vote for Xu Mengyu.
请给徐梦予投一票
Okay.
好
Thank you.
谢谢
Hi.
你好
Mengyu.
梦姐
Who put you up to this?
谁让你做这些的
Just wanna get some votes for you.
我就想给你投个票
I don't need that.
我不需要
So embarrassing.
你丢不丢人啊
You wouldn't get it.
你不会懂的
You know.
你说你
I was finally getting into
我好不容易才对学习
the swing of studying.
提出那么就一丁点兴趣
And now that you've been elected,
你就当选了
no time to help me with my studies.
都没有时间管我学习了
Looks like
那看来
I'm holding you back.
确实是我阻挡你进步了
Of course not.
那没有
But
只不过
the sadness in my heart
我心里的那种惋惜之情
flows like a mighty river.
就犹如那江水滔滔
It's truly upsetting.
难过上眉梢
For real?
真难过
Okay, I see.
行 那我明白了
What did you say?
你刚才说
About your sadness?
惋惜之情犹如什么来着
What do you mean?
你什么意思
What happened?
不是 你什么情况
Jinghui!
灰哥 灰哥
Hey, mate.
干什么 干什么
Calm down! I'm still breathing here.
喊什么喊 我没死呢
Attention, please.
各位同学
An announcement.
现在插播一条通知
Due to personal reasons,
由于个人原因
Ling Dong from Class 5, Grade 2
我校高二五班凌冬同学
has withdrawn from the selection.
退出才艺大赛投票选拔
The ranking has been adjusted.
目前比赛排名顺延
Xiao Xiaohua, in second place,
排名第二的肖小画同学
is far ahead.
高票领先
Hello, everyone.
你好 大家好
I'm Xiao Xiaohua from Class 5, Grade 2.
我是高二五班的肖小画
Hi, what are you doing?
嗨 录什么呢
Mom, you scared me!
妈 你吓我一跳
I'm filming a video.
录视频呢
Yeah?
是吗
Don't peek.
你别看了
School assignment.
学校要求的
I brought you some fruit.
妈妈给你送水果
Thanks, just leave it there.
我不吃 你放下吧
I'm curious.
看看没关系嘛
Stop there.
不嘛
Alright.
好好好
Forget it.
不录了不录了
Hi, guys.
同学们好
I'm Chen Luyang.
我是陈璐阳
I'm gonna recite the number
接下来是我的表演
used to
π
calculate the size of circles...
三点一四
Hi, everyone.
大家好
I'm Lan Jinghui from Class 5, Grade 2.
我是高二五班的兰靖灰
I have no intention of participating
我对才艺大赛
in the talent show, thank you.
没有任何想法 谢谢